onlinehomeincome.in 2019-07-25

# Privacy Policy - Online Home Income Blog

## Privacy Policy Statement:

We, at ONLINEHOMEINCOME.IN says, thank you for your trust in us.

We respect your privacy and assure for maintaining accuracy, confidentiality and security of your personal information safety which had been collected on our website through any methods.

The information we collect on our website is used only for sending information about our website products and our sponsors offer or to get in touch with you.

We, in any situation, won’t release or sell your private personal information to anyone outside by any means.

As our site come under Blogging category, we are in the necessity to link to other websites.

As far as different sites concerned, each site may have its own privacy policy for their members or visitors.

So before you submit a form to that sites please read their privacy policy statements.

### Who We Are:

We at _www.onlinehomeincome.in_ is very much concerned about our site visitors safety towards their personally identifiable information.

I am Myilraj.G, Author, and Founder of _www.onlinehomeincome.in_. I am based at Coimbatore, Tamilnadu, India.

Basically, I am an engineer but turned into a blogger by profession and started this blog to share my own experience in Online Money Making.

In this blog, you will get the latest information about various online money making sources and also, Blogging Training Session conducted by myself.

### What Personal Data We Collect and Why We Collect it?

In our blog, we do not collect any sensitive data like credit card information, banking information, other finance-related and health-related information.

We normally collect our user’s name and email address to send notification emails and transactional emails about our blog articles.

Users when visiting our site should understand that we collect only this two information and even though they are at our visitors will.

If they don’t want to subscribe to your blog, they can leave the email subscription empty.

Every user can subscribe or unsubscribe any time by clicking a subscription and/or unsubscription link to the bottom.

### Comments:

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media:

There is no point of the node were available on our site ( _www.onlinehomeincome.in_ ) that let our visitors upload any images, pictures, videos, and any digital media.

### Contact Forms:

We have placed a WP-Forms powered contact form on our blog for our visitors to reach us for any queries, doubts, or clarifications.

In the form, the users are requested to mention their name, email address only and that is only for pure official communication purpose.

We will use them for any marketing or commercial purpose.

### Cookies:

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to save your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

#### Log Files:

Like many other Web sites, www.onlinehomeincome.in makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’ analytics.

The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks.

This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Embedded Contents from other websites:

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie:

→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on _www.onlinehomeincome.in_.  
→ Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to _www.onlinehomeincome.in_ and other sites on the Internet.  
→ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Our Advertising Partners:

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….  
→Google  
→Commission Junction  
→Amazon  
→Adbrite  
→Yahoo! Publisher Network

_While each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here: Privacy Policies. You may consult this listing to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of www.onlinehomeincome.in._

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on www.onlinehomeincome.in and which are sent directly to your browser.

They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

www.onlinehomeincome.in has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

### Third Party Privacy Policies:

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

www.onlinehomeincome.in’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

You may find a comprehensive listing of these privacy policies and their links here: [Privacy Policy Links](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/privacy-policy-links "Privacy Policy Links").

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. [What Are Cookies?](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/what-are-cookies)

### Children’s Information:

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

www.onlinehomeincome.in does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that www.onlinehomeincome.in has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (through contact page) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### Disclaimer:

All the contents that are listed in _www.onlinehomeincome.in_ are provided “As-Is” and “As-When”.

We assume no responsibility for any misleads under any circumstances. You agree that you will not reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, trade, resell or exploit any part of our website or service for any commercial purposes.

www.onlinehomeincome.in reserves right to modify or alter any content may be discontinued temporarily or permanently with or without prior notice.

www.onlinehomeincome.in does not provide responsibility for any means or kinds of losses either directly or indirectly for any individuals or any others visiting or trying our products through our website.

We will not provide assurance for any warranties, or guarantees or representations to the products found in our website and users are solely responsible for his activities with the advertiser whom they contacting regarding any purchase or trial of a product.

Disclaimer: www.onlinehomeincome.in is not associated with any of the websites listed in PTC Database or SURVEY sites and it is totally up to the individuals to understand the concept and implement it at his/her own risk.

We also make no promises or claims that how much you will earn every month and all the details presently provided about your earnings are just to give you a basic idea of the business.

www.onlinehomeincome.in is not responsible for any direct or indirect loss of his/her health or wealth in trying the products or using the services listed in our website and everything is purely dependent on the person using or trying the product or undertaking the business opportunities.

Kindly note that this website does not provide any Get Rich Quick Income Schemes or any HYIP programs and all your earnings are purely depend on the individual capacity.

Many factors are important in determining your actual results and no guarantees will be made that you will achieve results as like others using our website.

You can make money more or less depending on your involvement and dedication in your work by using our listed opportunities on our website. And it also depends on a variety of factors.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin [at] onlinehomeincome [dot] in.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only:

At www.onlinehomeincome.in we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by www.onlinehomeincome.in and how we use it.

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there.

This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

#### Consent:

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

#### Update:

Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
